thanks for the calls Market is offer
good 60 70 points from the highest
levels of the morning so let's say it's
still very very early into the trading
session let's however shift the focus to
the commodity markets and figure out how
they're grappling with the morning after
so to speak Manisha is here with us
Manisha good morning so what do you have
your eye on well the overall Commodities
are the sector because we started on a
very positive note the dollar Index has
come off it's high we did see seven week
highs in the previous week itself after
the kind of data that U.S allowed let
out but uh with the bank's concerns
we've seen dollar Index decline the
tangible Commodities have seen some
buying come back that's the dollar index
for you half a percent of a decline on
to that one and we also are looking at
the U.S payroll data while it was higher
than the street expectation but not as
blisteringly strong as we saw in the
month of January and that clearly has
been supportive as well apart from that
the U.S banking crisis now has pushed
the FED into softening hawkish stands is
what the markets believe so last week
while there was an 80 of a probability
of a 50 basis point rate hike now there
is a 70 probability of for 25 basis rate
hike so that's how fast it really seems
to be changing there so when you look at
the steel prices we're trading at an
eight month highs uh iron ore price is
trading at a seven month highs the
Chinese demand also seems to have
improved especially as we are getting
into a peak construction season which
begins from next quarter and then it
also is about the expectation that China
will announce more fiscal support as it
has pledged and reiterated that is what
also seems to be supporting markets in
Precious Metals you have gold prices
trading at a four week high silver is
trading at a two-week highs copper
prices have jumped up quite strongly as
well so we are back above four dollars
crude prices which fell four percent in
the previous week also are trading on a
firmer note here here as well what or
else is supporting the crude is the fact
that the U.S oil and gas recount is now
at 590 which is the lowest since June so
there is lower Supply that we've seen
coming from U.S much of the record highs
that we saw in the pre-covered era there
but what the street will clearly watch
out now is the U.S CPI data that comes
in on Tuesday and that's going to be the
most important event ahead of the U.S
fed meeting that's on 22nd of March as
long as long as we don't have any more
bank failures before that right jobs
data was the most important and then sap
have